Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 3: Architectural Drawings (Oversized), 1893-1993; 6 boxes; 212 folders
  - OPP and ENG Only (Survey Plans), dates not examined; 4 folders
    - D-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-11, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - Engineering Quad, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-1, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-2, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - E-11, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - G-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - G-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - G-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - G-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - G-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - G-11, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - H-11, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - I-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - I-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - I-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - J-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - J-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - J-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - K-2, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - K-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - K-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - L-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - L-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 81)
    - Princeton University Campus Maps (Control Points), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-1, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-2, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - F-11, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - G-1, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - G-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
    - G-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 80)
  - Brauer (Drawings), dates not examined; 4 folders
    - Class 1989 Ivy Stone Full Size Layout, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Jones Hall Alteration (First, Second Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Rowing Tank Building (Window Detail), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Chancellor Green Student Center (Detail of Office Partitions), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - 1901 Laughlin Hall Alteration (Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Jones Hall Alteration (First, Second Floors - Master Color Set), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Deans House (First Floor - Scheme A), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Lowrie House Alterations (Second Floor Bathrooms - Schemes A and B), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - James Forrestal Campus Building Number 9A (Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Guyot Hall (First Floor, Partial Plan Showing Women's Lounge), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Deans House (Second Floor - Scheme B), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Detail of Library Shelving, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Marble Leg for President Samuel Smith Monument (Full Size Detail), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Edith Chapel, Lawrenceville School (Pulpit Lectern Modification and New Pulpit Lectern), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Deans House (Proposed Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - 18-40 Edwards Place (Porch Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Frick Chem Lab (Room 133 Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Joseph Henry House (Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Auxiliary Library (Book Stack Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Green Hall Annex Alterations (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Student Employment and Storage Building (Proposed Site Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Eisenhart Memorial Tower (Lounge), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - John MacLean House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Clio Railing, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Rock Magnetism Lab, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Clark Field Seating, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Eno Hall Inscription, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Rock Magnetism Lab (Proposed Site), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - 58 Murray Place (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous and Unidentified (Plaques, Drawings, and Floor Plans), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 82)
    - Green Hall Alteration, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Proposed Rock Magnetism Lab, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - 1879 Hall (Stair), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Rapliano Memorial Bench, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Russel Memorial Bench, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - McCosh 50 (Faculty Lounge), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Green Annex (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Lab, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Deans House (Second Floor - Scheme A), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Fine Hall (Basement), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Chem Lab Addition (Basement), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Palmer Laboratory (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Student Employment and Storage Building (Preliminary Site Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Stanhope Hall (Site Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous (Plaques and Pictures), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous (Plaques), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 84)
    - Drawings for Plaques (Contents Unidentified), undated; 3 folders (Folder Oversize folder 85, Folder 86, Folder 87)
  - Floorplans of Campus Buildings, dates not examined; 2 folders
    - Graduate College (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth, Sixth Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Henry Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Fourth Fifth Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Jadwin Hall (B, A, First Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Lockhart Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Lourie-Love Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - 1942 Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Lowrie House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - McCarter Theater (Basement, Stage Level, Tower One and Two, Balcony), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - McCormick/Art Museum (Basement, A, First, M, Second, Third, Fourth Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - McCosh Infirmary (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - McCosh Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Murray-Dodge Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Nassau Hall (Basement, First, SEcond, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Palmer Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Peyton Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Pyne Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Robertson Hall (Lower, Main Levels), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 88)
    - Dillon Gym (C, B, A, First, Second, Tower), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - E-Quad, dates not examined; 1 folder
      - Library 1900 (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - C Wing/Beggs Hall (First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - E Wing/MacLean Hall (First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - A Wing/Hayes Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - D Wing/Duffield Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - B Wing/Brackett Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
      - J Wing (First, Second, Third, Fourth Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - East Pyne (First, Second, Third, Tower), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Elementary Particle Lab West (Basement, First), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Energy Research Lab (Basement, Ground, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Firestone Library (A, C, Main, Second, Third, Penthouse, and Towers), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Forbes College Addition (First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Foulke Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 76)
    - Alexander Hall (Balcony Level), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - 126 Alexander Street (First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Architecture Building (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Architecture Lab (Main Floor, Basement), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Auxiliary Library (Mechanical, First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Bowen Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Caldwell Field House (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Cambell Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Center for Jewish Life (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Chapel (Basement, First, Triforium), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Chilled Water Plant (Main Floor, Mezzanine), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Computer Center (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Computer Science Building (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
    - Dickinson Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 75)
  - Jon Hlafter (Floor Plans and Other Maps), dates not examined; 2 folders
    - John MacLean House (Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Palmer Hall (First Floor - Two Copies), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - 106 Alexander Street (Exterior, Attic), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Fine Hall (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Princeton Inn (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Harvard University Map, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Dial Lodge (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Green Hall (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Life Sciences Complex (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Princeton University Press (Parking Lot), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Princeton University Library (Plaza Redevelopment), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Holder Hall (Courtyard), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Facilities of the PUYC (Additions), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - 35 University Place (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Princeton University Kosher Kitchen, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Physics Hi Energy Research Relocation Study, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Green Hall Renovation (Timetable), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - New South Dumpster Relocation, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Frick Laboratory (Lab Number Four Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Frick Laboratory (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Office Building and Warehouse Proposal, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Unidentified Drawing, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Frick Laboratory (Lab Number Four Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Guyot Hall (Room A-55 Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Frick Laboratory (Lab Number Four Alterations), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Green Hall Renovations (Timetable, Design Program, Scope of Work), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 89)
    - Green Hall Renovations (Schematic Design), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Alexander Hall (Basement Addition), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Unidentified Drawing, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Presbyterian Church (Land), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Alexander Hall (Pictures), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Alexander Hall (Map), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Alexander Hall (Cross Section), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Guyot Hall Renovations (Schematic Design), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - McCarter Theater (Map), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Alexander Hall (Map), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Forbes College (Map), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Princeton University Maps, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
    - Prospect House (Exterior), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 90)
  - Floor Plans and Other Maps, dates not examined; 3 folders; 2 items
    - Walker Hall (Second Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Wilcox Hall (Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Woolworth Music Center (Ground, First, Second, Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - 171 Broadmead (Basement), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Route US 1/Penns Neck Area Improvement Study Map, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - E-Quad (Landscape, Lighting Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Materials Science Center (Revised Plaza Details), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Route 1 Corridor Study, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - 1979 Hall (Addition), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Princeton University Map, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 91)
    - Class of 1946 (Garden), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Elm Drive (Disabled Improvements), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Route 1 Corridor Study (Property Distribution), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Princeton Area Map, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Princeton University Map, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Brown/1903/Feinberg (Walk Improvements), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Armory (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Wilson College (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Little/Green/Dillon (Parking Lot), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Little Hall (Elm Drive Improvements), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Butler College (Volleyball Court), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Prospect House (Dumpster Location), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Lawrence Court (New Walks and Steps), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Third World Center (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Butler College (Northern Entrance Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Graduate College (Relocated Walk), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Henry Moore Sculpture (Bluestone Terrace), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Prospect Garden (Approach), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - New South Plaza (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - The Lowrie House (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - North East Corner of Campus (Landscaping Layout), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Baker Rink (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Prospect Avenue (Planting), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Woodrow Wilson School (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Guyot Hall (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - New South (Proposed Plaza), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Stevenson Hall (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Geology Library (Landscaping), undated; 1 item
    - Prospect Avenue (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Woodrow WIlson School (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Princeton Inn Courtyard (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Guyot Hall (Terrace Development), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Geology Library Courtyard (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Prospect Gardens (Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 92)
    - Robertson Hall (Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 93)
    - Spelman Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Roof), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 93)
    - Walker Hall (Basement, First), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 93)
    - 1879 Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 93)
  - White (Floor Plans and Other Maps; Campus Map Negatives), 1961-1972; 4 folders
    - Unidentified Item, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Building 9A (Forrestal Campus), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Health Physics Group (Forrestal Barn - Proposed Layout), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Gilson House (Forrestal Campus - Proposed Layout), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Geology Library Feasability Study (Guyot Museum Location), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Computer Center, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Fine Hall (Library, Plaza, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth, Sixth, Seventh, Eighth, Ninth, Tenth, Eleventh, Twelfth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Jadwin Physical Laboratory (A, B, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - New South (Second, Third, Fifth, Sixth, Seventh), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Jadwin Gymnasium Seating Plan, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - 1969 Co-educational Site Selection, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Patton Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Princeton Inn (Proposed Addition), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Palmer Hall/Gest Library (Bulletin Board), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Alexander Hall (Toilets), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Campus Maps, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Room Type as Percentage of Total Non-Residential Space, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Total Non-Residential Space per Student, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Lot 22, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - University Place (Parking), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Campus Center (Proposed Improvements), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Computer Center (Basement, Ground, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Third World Center (Proposed Site Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Osborn Club House Redecoration (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Wawa Market (Exterior), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Geology Library (Main Floor, Mezzanine), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 94)
    - Campus Map Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 96)
    - 35 University Place (First, Second, Third Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 96)
    - Unidentified Drawings, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 95)
    - Portfolio of Various Projects, 1961-1972; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 97)
  - Art Museum (Proposed alteration), dates not examined; 1 folder 1 pencil rendering (Folder Oversize folder 98)
    undated, unsigned, possibly Klauder.
  - Art Museum, dates not examined; 1 folder 9 drawings on linen (Folder Oversize folder 98)
    A. Page Brown.
  - Biological Laboratory (Class of 1877), dates not examined; 1 folder 9 elevations and floor plans in black and brown ink; 2 blueprints 1st floor plan; 2 blueprints 2nd floor plan (Folder Oversize folder 99)
    Watercolor rendering by A. Page Brown.
  - Brokaw Field Memorial, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 99)
    Rendering of stairway and wall with inscription. Voorhees, Walker, Foley and Smith.
  - Caldwell Field House, dates not examined; 1 folder 2 reproductions; 2 floor plans with schedule of interior finish (Folder Oversize folder 100)
    Steinmann, Cain and White.